http://www.battlefieldsports.com/privacy

Blog
Battlefield Sports Privacy PolicyData Protection Department Shop 6, 2 Commercial DriveShailer Park Q 4128AUSTRALIAContact: Nicole LanderPhone 1800 Book Us (1800 266 587)Fax 1300 666 549info@battlefieldsports.com RELEASED June 18th, 2002UPDATED August 16th, 2011UPDATED May 16th, 2018 (minor amendments November 7th, 2019) Privacy Policy: Battlefield SportsWelcome To Battlefield Sports Battlefield Sports makes live gaming equipment and markets our goods/services via the Battlefield Sports website (the "Site") the business is run by Scapequest Pty Ltd (the "Company" or "we" or "us") for users of the goods and services ("you"). Our sister company Pathfinder Events Pty Ltd runs live games and rents gaming equipment. Brand names include "Laser Tag in a Box" and "Laser Skirmish" and "Battlefield LIVE". This privacy policy sets out our policy concerning info that is collected from visitors to the site and users of our goods and/or services. Under the applicable law, Battlefield Sports is the "data controller" of personal data collected by us. Info We CollectWhen you interact with us we may collect info from you, as described below. Info you provide: We collect info from you when you voluntarily provide it, such as when you register for access to our marketing documents or the Battlefield Sports University. This info may include but not limited to username, email address, images or other content you send via email, online forms or the chat feature. Other InfoCookies: We employ cookies and similar tech to keep track of your local computer's settings such as which account you have logged into. Also, we may use tech such as single-pixel gifs, like the Facebook pixel, to record log data such as open rates for emails. We may use third-party web site analytic tools such as Google Analytics what also employ cookies to collect info concerning your usage. You can disable cookies by changing your web browser settings. Advertisements: You may see us advertised on other applications or web sites. After clicking on one of these ads, the advertising platforms such as Facebook may collect info for optimizing advertising campaigns. Data Collected Automatically: When you interact with us we received and store certain info such as an IP address, and which newsletters or documents you have chosen to subscribe to.Aggregated Info: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve our users we may research customer feedback. The research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, we may then post research results on our blog. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and/or government agencies, and other third parties for other lawful purposes. Where The Info Is ProcessedThe company is based in Australia. We have agents in the USA and other places. No matter where you are located you consent to the processing and transferring of your info in and to the US and other countries. The laws of Australia and other country's government data collection may not be as comprehensive as the laws of the country where you live.  Our Use of Your InfoWe use the info you provide in a manner that is consistent with the policy. If you provide info for a certain reason, we may use that info in connect with that reason. For example, if you contact us by email, we will use the info you provide to answer your question or resolve your issue. If you provide info to get access to our goods/services we will use your info to provide you with access to such and to monitor your use of such. We may use your info collected to help us improve the content and functionality of our goods/services or to better understand our users and to improve our goods/services. Our Legal Basis For Handling Your Personal DataThe laws in some jurisdictions demand companies to tell you about the legal grounds they rely on to use your data. To the extent those laws apply, our legal grounds are as follows: To honor our contractual commitments to you. We strive to meet our contractual obligations to our users or to take steps at a user's request in anticipation of entering into a contract. To enable a legitimate interest. We strive to provide safe and enjoyable user experience, we aim to provide good customer service, marketing such as sending emails or other communication to let you know about new features or offers, protecting our users, personnel & property, analyzing and improving our business, processing job candidates, or managing legal issues. To manage legal compliance. We need to the user or disclosed personal data in certain ways to comply with our legal obligations. To provide the interests of an individual or others, e.g. we may collect or share personal data to help resolve an urgent medical issue or to comply with a government order, for example ASIO, ASIS or an enforcement agency performing a lawful national security function asks Battlefield Sports not to provide access on the basis that providing access would be likely to cause damage to the national security of Australia.Our Disclosure of Your InfoOur company is not in the business of selling your info. We consider this info to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain situations in which we may share your info with certain third parties. As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or business assets. In the event of a business sale, merger, dissolution or similar your info may be part of the transferred assets. We may also share your info with our related companies for purposes consistent with this policy. Like many companies, we occasionally engage other businesses or individuals to perform certain business-related functions. We may disclose your info if required to do so by law or in good faith that such action is necessary to comply with that legal obligation, to protect and defend the rights or property of the company, to protect the personal safety of users or the public, or to protect against legal liability.  We may share aggregated or non-personally identifiable info with our partners or others for business purposes. Unsolicited Info You may provide us with ideas for new goods/services or modifications to existing goods/services, and other unsolicited submissions. All unsolicited info shall be deemed to be non-confidential and we shall be free to reproduce, use, disclosed, and distribute such unsolicited info to others without limitation or attribution.KidsPurchasing our goods/services are for users of majority age. We do not knowingly collect personal info from kids. If you are a parent or guardian of a child and believe he or she has disclosed personal info to us please contact us at info@battlefieldsports.com. For citizens of the European Economic Area, where the processing of personal info is based on consent, Battlefield Sports will not knowingly engage in that processing for users of minority age as deemed by applicable data protection law. If we learn that we are engaged in that processing we will halt such processing and will take reasonable measure to promptly remove applicable info from our records. Links To Other Web SitesThis policy only applies to us. We may contact links to other web sites not operated or controlled by us. Links from us to these third-party sites do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed them. We recommend contacting those other sites directly for info on their privacy policies. Further, payment transactions are processed directly via bank wire or credit card or Paypal. Please note that these organizations have their privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for those policies.Data RetentionIn general, we retain personal data for so long as it may be relevant to the purposes identified herein. To dispose of personal info we may delete it or take other appropriate steps. Data, however, may persist in copies made for backup and business continuity purposes for some additional time. Data Security Security of your data is important to us. We take reasonable steps to protect the info provided for loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Your Data Rights We believe that users should be treated equally no matter where you live. You can update your information or unsubscribe from certain emails by clicking the unsubscribe link they contain. You can opt-out from certain cookie processing by following the instructions linked above. People from the EEA and other jurisdictions have certain legal rights to obtain confirmation of whether we hold personal data about them, to access personal data we hold about them and to obtain its correction, update, amendment or deletion in appropriate circumstances. They may also object to our uses or disclosures of personal data or request a restriction on its processing or withdraw any consent. Though such actions typically will not have retroactive effect. They also will not affect our ability to continue processing data in lawful ways. If you would like to access the data we have about you please submit a data access request by sending us an email to info@battlefieldsports.com with the subject line "data access request". We will then start the process and provide you the personal data we have on you within 30 business days of receiving your email. You can request we correct, update, amend the personal data we have on you or request other modifications by emailing us at info@battlefieldsports.com with the subject line "data modification request". Please include in your message an explanation of what data subject right you are seeking to exercise. For your protection, we may take steps to verify identity before responding or actioning your request. If you are in the EEA you have the right to opt-out of all of our processing of your data for direct marketing purposes. To exercise this right, please email us at info@battlefieldsports.com with the subject line "EEA Opt-Out of Data Processing". Or you may simply click the unsubscribe link in any of our marketing emails. Rights and options described above are subject to limitations and exceptions under applicable law. In addition to these rights, you have the right to complain with the relevant supervisory authority. If you are unhappy with the way that we respond to your requests, or in the way we have used your data, you have the right to complain with the Information Commissioner's Office at https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/report-a-breach/We do, however, encourage you to contact us first and we will do our very best to resolve your issue. Changes To This Policy We reserve the right to update or modify this policy at any time. These changes may be made from time to time and without prior notice. Please check out this policy periodically, and especially before you provide us with any info. When the policy is updated is the date indicated above will also be updated. Your continued use of our goods/services after any changes or revisions to this policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of our revised policy. Get In Contact With Us You are welcome to contact us if you have any questions about this policy or our info practices. Please email us at info@battlefieldsports.com with the subject line "privacy policy query". The Battlefield Sports’ website is available at www.BattlefieldSports.com If you have any questions or need clarification about this Privacy Policy please contact the Data Production Officer via info@battlefieldsports.com
For a printable Download of this privacy policy, click here.
Copyright © 2020 Battlefield Sports.
Cookie Policy
